{"active_questions": [{"question": "Jaka jutro pogoda", "correct": "B", "answers": ["fajna", "s\u0142aba", "\u015brednia", "dobra"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Niemiec?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Berlin", "B:Monachium", "C:Frankfurt", "D:Hamburg"]}, {"question": "Jaka dzispogoda?", "correct": "C", "answers": ["A:gowno", "B:gawa", "C:gowadaw", "D:pizda"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka jutro pogoda", "correct": "B", "answers": ["fajna", "s\u0142aba", "\u015brednia", "dobra"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka jutro4 pogoda", "correct": "B4", "answers": ["faj4na", "s\u0142aba", "\u015brednia", "dobra"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka jutro4 pogoda", "correct": "B4", "answers": ["faj4na", "s\u0142aba", "\u015brednia", "dobra"]}, {"question": "Jaka jutro4 pogoda", "correct": "B4", "answers": ["faj4na", "s\u0142aba", "\u015brednia", "dobra"]}, {"question": "Jaka jutro pogoda", "correct": "B", "answers": ["fajna", "s\u0142aba", "\u015brednia", "dobra"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "dwadwa", "correct": "D", "answers": ["dwad", "dwadaw", "dwad", "dwadaw"]}, {"question": "Gowno", "correct": "D", "answers": ["dwad", "dwadaw", "dwad", "dwadaw"]}], "no_active_questions": [{"question": "Jaka jutro4 pogoda", "correct": "B4", "answers": ["faj4na", "s\u0142aba", "\u015brednia", "dobra"]}, {"question": "Jaka dzispogoda?", "correct": "C", "answers": ["A:gowno", "B:gawa", "C:gowadaw", "D:pizda"]}, {"question": "Jaka jutro pogoda", "correct": "B", "answers": ["fajna", "s\u0142aba", "\u015brednia", "dobra"]}, {"question": "Jaka jutro4 pogoda", "correct": "B4", "answers": ["faj4na", "s\u0142aba", "\u015brednia", "dobra"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Niemiec?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Berlin", "B:Monachium", "C:Frankfurt", "D:Hamburg"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka dzispogoda?", "correct": "C", "answers": ["A:gowno", "B:gawa", "C:gowadaw", "D:pizda"]}, {"question": "Jaka dzispogoda?", "correct": "C", "answers": ["A:gowno", "B:gawa", "C:gowadaw", "D:pizda"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Niemiec?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Berlin", "B:Monachium", "C:Frankfurt", "D:Hamburg"]}, {"question": "Jaka jutro4 pogoda", "correct": "B4", "answers": ["faj4na", "s\u0142aba", "\u015brednia", "dobra"]}, {"question": "Jaka dzispogoda?", "correct": "C", "answers": ["A:gowno", "B:gawa", "C:gowadaw", "D:pizda"]}, {"question": "Jaka dzispogoda?", "correct": "C", "answers": ["A:gowno", "B:gawa", "C:gowadaw", "D:pizda"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka dzispogoda?", "correct": "C", "answers": ["A:gowno", "B:gawa", "C:gowadaw", "D:pizda"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka dzispogoda?", "correct": "C", "answers": ["A:gowno", "B:gawa", "C:gowadaw", "D:pizda"]}, {"question": "Jaka dzispogoda?", "correct": "C", "answers": ["A:gowno", "B:gawa", "C:gowadaw", "D:pizda"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "dwadwa", "correct": "B", "answers": ["", "", "", ""]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Niemiec?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Berlin", "B:Monachium", "C:Frankfurt", "D:Hamburg"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Niemiec?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Berlin", "B:Monachium", "C:Frankfurt", "D:Hamburg"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Polski?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Warszawa", "B:Krak\u00f3w", "C:Lublin", "D:Pozna\u0144"]}, {"question": "Jaka jutro4 pogoda", "correct": "B4", "answers": ["faj4na", "s\u0142aba", "\u015brednia", "dobra"]}, {"question": "Jaka jest stolica Niemiec?", "correct": "A", "answers": ["A:Berlin", "B:Monachium", "C:Frankfurt", "D:Hamburg"]}]}